Hi guys, it's me again, Clara, and
welcome to my YouTube channel, Clara
Trump.
And by the way guys, um I would like to
request and please watch, like and
subscribe to my YouTube channel. Please
also follow me and my Facebook, um
Instagram, Twitter, also here in my YT
channel. Um always remember it's Clara
Champurado. Y lang. You can see me there
now. Okay. And stay tuned pala guys cuz
we're going to draw now our lucky pick n
man worth 1,000 pesos of lasada mystery
box.
[Music]
For tonight's video what we're going to
do is we're going to review
a brand of sticker. Speaking of that, um
I remember this is actually my first
speaker. This one
first purchase nam husband co. Um this
is the JBL mini. Um,
we only use this indoor cuz the sound is
not really good cuz you know it's mahina
and then parang wala bass parang ganun
and actually this is actually an a
Bluetooth connectiv uh connectivity and
then 2 years we switched to JBL charge
3. I know everyone of you are familiar
with this charge uh with this speaker.
This speaker is actually it's absolutely
good as in super good cuz this is water
resistant. But take note, I'm not going
to review this this this brand. What
we're going to do is we're going to
review another brand.
This is the small one and this is the
medium. So what we're going to do is
we're going to review a bigger one. So
I'm going to put this aside
for now. Okay. Ready guys
[Music]
speaker
and meet sorry Kilbert 2.
It takes me back from the pastural.
Okay. So you guys are you ready now?
Let's open this one now. Hey
[Music]
open
sticker
lock n cardboard and then ta
open na anal
talaga na bagago.
Okay. First off is when you open this
one, you have this yan. You have this
yung ano
naan para for safety
item secure safe unit.
And what a good thing about this
dust bag.
[Music]
Yeah.
para sa
protection sik.
Okay, this box um this unit actually
includes the item itself. It has the
manual um the legal safety information
and also the power cord here.
Here's the Marshall Cilbert 3. I'm going
to take out first. Here's the inclusion.
Yeah.
Also this one the legal and safety.
Oh guys
[Laughter]
research ny na lang. Okay an
cordal
naman.
Yeah naman. Well actually hopeful naman
inside.
Okay. So, let's talk about
what's new with you.
[Music]
Okay. Um, this Marshall speaker is
so special cuz it offers a lot of things
like um this item is not so very migat.
It's not magan.
This is just only 2.5 kilos.
caring
[Music]
like what I've mentioned I'm going to
show it to you closely or close up
speaker
front view of this speaker you will see
this um solid metal wire mesh wire nally
um mini microphone and this kind of the
this kind of design is to mash uh
Marshall. At the same time, it's it
feels like it's echoing the legacy of
rock and roll. Not only at the front
where the sound's coming from, it's also
um coming from at the at the back.
This speaker is actually uh a
multidirectional sound. You can see on
the right side the belove one that's
also a speaker. And then on the left
side which is looks like uh pa oblong or
sorry letter v pa oblong um that is
where the bass is you bass sound jang
gagal. Okay when you go down you will
see the aux there that's where you're
going to um connect your jack in case
that you don't want to use your your
Bluetooth. And then on this one you will
see there where a small um nakat that's
where you're going to put your power
cord par whenever you want to charge
your speaker
on the side view of this speaker you
will see how elegant the look is on
leather nto actually this is not a real
leather um Kilburn 2 actually confirmed
that there are no animal harmed on this
product and at the same time you You
will see the four um flush mounted
corner cups that is uh that is parang
one of their design. At the same time it
secure the unit
to any kind of um in any kind adventure
or any adventure
speaker
top view. So y panel where
okay I'm going to show it to you the
closer look this one an um slowly by
slowly you will see the panel here or
the dials where you uh which which are
the the volume the bass and the treble
which is pretty depend
[Music]
So
battery indicator this one I'm charging
this speaker as you can see while I'm
charging it
indicator. So from one bar going to the
full bar it's meaning it's charging.
For your quick reference, as you can
see, I used my cell phone um 11 Pro Max
um as a comparison
height.
iPhone 11.
Okay. So, now we're going to play music.
This this clip edited. you will hear the
exact music um or the exact sound of
this speaker. And by the way guys um the
the the songs of course
music per I'm telling it to you guys.
I'm really assuring you the sound is
really good. So listen, I'm going to
show you I'm going to give you three
kinds of songs or three sounds.
[Music]
Good clean.
Heat. Heat. N.
[Music]
[Applause]
[Laughter]
[Music]
[Applause]
an Phantom Marshall Private.
Okay guys, since we're done in our
product review, what we're going to do
next is
we're going to announce the lucky pick
winner.
Okay, I know man everyone are familiar
now from our from
my first video I mentioned there a n
isang winner from the first 100
subscribers n
channel po and right now is we're going
to announce it now and thank you guys
for always supporting me and for
subscribing I already have 153
subscribers and I'm also looking forward
I hope you guys can join me
to road 250 subscribers naman. Okay, so
we're going going to we're going to
start now. Okay.
Um what the app I'm going to use now to
pick for the winner is you spin the
wheel app. Um I think some of you or few
of you are familiar now with this app
now. So I'm not going to explain it
anyway. So I'm just going to use this na
lang pair to all the people or for
parare those of first 100 subscribers.
Okay
here guys. Okay
ba against the light
[Music]
backlight. Ayan very perfect. Okay. Um
going to click this one now.
Wait a bang.
Okay guys, here I'm going to click this
now.
[Music]
Yay!
Congratulations, Raymond FG. You just
won worth of 1,000 pesos mystery box
from Lada. Please PM me or I'm going to
message you
details mo where I'm going to ship the
item with you or where I'm going to put
the shipping address sada
app when I order your mystery box. But
right after this video, I'm going to
order now your mystery box.
[Applause]
[Music]